in.canon 2019-08-27

# Privacy policy - Canon India

### Acceptance

This website ("Canon Website") is provided to you by Canon Singapore Pte. Ltd.("Canon") on the following terms and conditions ("Terms and Conditions"). By accessing any page on this Canon Website, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. These Terms and Conditions may be updated by Canon from time to time without prior notice. You should check the Terms and Conditions for updates each time you access the Canon Website.

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy/statement of CIPL (“Policy”) is made in relation to the information collected by CIPL from its Employees, Customers, Vendors, Dealers (“Disclosing Party”) and specifies:

  * the kind of Information that CIPL will collect from the Disclosing Party;
  * the use of the collected information by CIPL and any third parties appointed by CIPL towards usage of such information; and
  * the security measures/ protocol that are adopted by CIPL to protect Disclosing Party’s Information so collected by CIPL.

This Policy lays down the methods adopted by CIPL to collect and use Disclosing Party’s Personal Information, including the information shared by the Disclosing Party towards any program & services as well as other information captured by CIPL and other third parties appointed by CIPL through the network server hosted in India for CIPL’s internal purposes (“ **Information** ”).

### Information Sharing

CIPL and/or any third party service provider appointed by CIPL shall use and share the Information which are received from the Disclosing Party, to track and analyze various statistical information, Disclosing Party’s usage of various Services provided by CIPL and for such other activities as set out below:

  * CIPL may use the Information to notify the Disclosing Party about new product releases and similar services, in accordance with this Policy. CIPL may pass the Disclosing Party’s contact information to any authorized third party for further follow-up communications related to Disclosing Party’s interests on some kind of Services provided by CIPL.
  * CIPL may use Disclosing Party’s Personal Data/Information to help create and personalize Information received from the Disclosing Party to facilitate the use of the Services, improve quality, carry out promotional and marketing activities by online advertising, e-mail marketing and SMS campaigns, track marketing campaign responsiveness and evaluate response rates.

#### Marketing  Activities

CIPL may engage in sales or product/service promotions. Both CIPL and any third party appointed by CIPL may provide services that may have access to Disclosing Party’s Information.  Either CIPL or its authorized service providers may provide the Disclosing Party with the product promotion information. CIPL shall be responsible for managing the use of the Disclosing Party’s Information collected for the sale and/or product promotion as per this Privacy Policy. The Disclosing Party shall review the privacy policy to address any questions they may have regarding CIPL’s handling of such information.

CIPL may disclose Disclosing Party’s Information as may be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside Disclosing Party’s country of residence; (b) to comply with applicable legal process; (c) to respond to any subpoena/requests from Court and / or government authorities, including public and government authorities outside Disclosing Party’s country of residence, for national security and/or law enforcement purposes without taking any prior consent.

CIPL may use, transfer, and disclose Disclosing Party’s information (including Personal data/information) that is collected for its internal purpose as well as for the purposes of its sales & marketing promotion, except where applicable law requires otherwise. If CIPL is required to treat any Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then CIPL will only use it in the manner as prescribed under applicable laws.

### Storage of Information

CIPL may collect and store the Disclosing Party’s personal Information on the server that is hosted in India having security practices/ protocol as required under Indian law.

### Cross Border Transfer of Information

CIPL shall ensure that Disclosing Party’s information is appropriately protected. Disclosing Party’s information may be transferred, accessed and stored globally as necessary for the use and disclosures as stated above in accordance with this policy. By providing the information, the Disclosing Party consents to CIPL transferring such information including its Personal Information to CIPL affiliates/ Group Companies globally and to third party entities which support CIPL or that provide its services to CIPL.

### Access, Correction, and Profile Updates

Disclosing Party may request CIPL to review, correct, update, or otherwise modify any of the Personal Information or to the use or process of any Personal Information that the Disclosing Party may have previously provided to CIPL for availing the Services by the Disclosing Party. The Disclosing Party shall have the ability to update their profile and related Personal Information at any time. To review, correct, update, or otherwise modify any of the Personal Information, the Disclosing Party shall write to CIPL at the following address:

 **[**<https://edge.canon.co.in/corporate/contact/> **]**

In the request, the Disclosing Party has to clearly identify the Personal Information that the Disclosing Party would like to have changed in CIPL’s database.

### Retention and Deletion

CIPL will retain Disclosing Party’s Information for as long as it is required by CIPL for the purposes outlined in this Policy and for a period of 5 years thereafter at its discretion, except when it is necessary to hold for a longer period in order to comply with the applicable legal obligations, resolve disputes to the extent permitted by law.

At the end of the retention period, CIPL will delete the Information to ensure that it cannot be reconstructed or read.

### Security

CIPL shall use reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards that are designed to protect Disclosing Party’s Information including the Images and Photographs shared by the Disclosing Party from the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

In addition, CIPL uses reasonable security protocols and mechanisms as prescribed under applicable laws to store/ exchange the transmission of Information.

In the event that Disclosing Party’s Information along with other information is acquired, or is reasonably believed to have been acquired, by an unauthorized person/ entities and applicable law requires notification, CIPL will notify the Disclosing Party by e-mail or postal mail. CIPL will give the Disclosing Party notice promptly as reasonably possible, consistent with the requirement under applicable law.

### Information Shared by the Disclosing Party

Disclosing Party understands and agrees that all information, including Personal Information, photographs, images, graphics, messages, or other materials, howsoever shared, transmitted to, from or through any medium, is the sole responsibility of the Disclosing Party. CIPL does not approve as well as not responsible for any violative Content including but not limited to any infringed content that may violate any third party IP right, any content that contains antinationalistic character / intent , nudity, sexually graphic material, or material that is otherwise deemed explicit by CIPL, any image content that promotes incest and bestiality, content that promotes pornography, child sexual abuse, promotes hate toward groups based on race or ethnic origin, religion, disability, gender, age, veteran status, and sexual orientation/gender identity or threats of violence against any person or group of people and any content that are considered for spamming or transmitting malware and viruses. Further, the Disclosing Party shall not submit or otherwise transmit any content that misleads or confuses any other user of the Website/Microsite including, but not limited to, encouraging another user to use the Website/Microsite in a way inconsistent with the terms and conditions, submit or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, or any other form of solicitation.

### Dispute Resolution

If the Disclosing Party has any complaints regarding CIPL’s compliance with this policy, the Disclosing Party should first write to complaints@canon.co.in. CIPL will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of Disclosing Party’s information in accordance with this policy. All disputes or differences related to this policy shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of Courts of Delhi and shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of India.

### Sensitive Information

Disclosing Party is advised not to send any Sensitive Information (such as Credit/Debit Card CVV number, any OTP generated during the transaction, government-issued or financial account numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, genetic, or biometric data).

### Policy Updates

CIPL may update this Policy from time to time. In the event CIPL make material changes that diminishes Disclosing Party’s rights or CIPL’s obligations under this Policy, CIPL will post a prominent notice any such change in the Policy notifying the Disclosing Parties when it is updated.
